- What's going on over there? - What is this?
- 그쪽은 무슨 일이야? - 이게 뭐야
It's chaos
난리인데
hello
안녕하십니까
- Today is the day of the final battle - Hello, today's guest.
- 오늘 결전의 날입니다 - 안녕하십니까 오늘의 게스트
I brought my pouch well
제가 파우치를 잘 챙겨왔고요
I'm really looking forward to it
아주 기대가 됩니다
The day of the decisive battle
결전의 날
- It's the day of the final battle - Hello, I was ticking*
- 결전의 날입니다 - 안녕하세요, 틱*을 찍고 있었습니다
hello
안녕하세요
- Yes, like this - It's the day of the final battle.
- 네, 이렇게 - 결전의 날입니다
We finally completed our mission in one month.
저희가 미션 수행을 드디어 한 달 만에
It's been two months since I did it
두 달 만에 하게 되었습니다
- Well, first of all... - Thank you for waiting for a long time.
- 아주, 일단... - 오래 기다리셨습니다
- Please spread the word about 'Idol Human Theater' widely, everyone. - That's right.
- '아이돌 인간극장'까지 널리 널리 퍼뜨려주세요 여러분들 - 그러니까요
We have to start now
우리 이제 시작해야 합니다
- Are you ready? - Let's get started.
- 준비되셨나요? - 시작을
- Start - Start
- 스타트
- Eunchae - But I have some plans for later.
- 은채 씨 - 근데 이후에 일정이 조금이나 있으니까
Please take good care of me though
잘 좀 부탁드려요 그래도
- Okay, okay, okay, okay - No, really.
- 알겠습니다 알겠습니다 알겠습니다 - 진짜 안 돼요
What's wrong? It's not what you do.
뭐가 안 돼, 언니가 하는 거 아니잖아
- This is a total must- - Just a moment
- 완전 가야죠 이거는 - 잠시만요
Wait a minute, there's one product
잠시만요, 제품이 하나
I'm going to practice after I finish, so
저도 끝나고 연습할 거거든요 그니까
So facial recognition and stuff like that
그래서 얼굴 인식 이런 거
Facial recognition like this
얼굴 인식 이렇게
Should I just take one shot?
한 번만 찍을까?
Just close your eyes
눈 감으면 되겠다
- I have cleansing tissues too - I'll take a short form.
- 제가 클렌징 티슈도 있어요 - 숏폼 좀 찍을게요
Excuse me, shouldn't you do it too, Mr. Kura?
잠시만요 꾸라 씨도 하셔야 되지 않나요?
I'm done right now
저는 바로 끝나요 바로
- It's over right away? - It's over once you put it on.
- 바로 끝나요? - 붙이면 끝이라서
- Eunchae is doing her makeup - She said she was waiting for Yoonjini's skills.
- 은채가 메이크업을 해요 - 윤진이의 솜씨를 기다린다고 하시는데
It may not be your skill, you guys
솜씨가 아닐 수도 있어요 여러분
okay
오케이
Okay, let's try lifting some of the bangs first.
자, 일단 앞머리를 좀 걷어볼까요?
- No, why? - Why?
- 아니요 왜 - 왜
- Why are you here? - What should I do?
- 왜 눈이 여긴데 - 어떻게 해
okay
알겠어
- The eyes is here. - Okay.
- 눈이 여긴데요 - 알겠어
- No, don't try to ruin me too much. - Okay.
- 아니 날 너무 망가트리려고 하지 마
- I'm a celebrity, but - Okay, okay.
- 나름 연예인이에요 그래도 - 알겠어요 알겠어요
all right
알겠어요
- We are idols before we are comedians - This cute
- 저희 개그우먼이기 전에 아이돌이에요 - 이 깜찍한
- This is Kura's sister. - Is this Kura's?
- 이건 꾸라 언니 거예요 - 이건 꾸라 씨 거예요?
I get it, I get it, it's really noisy in the shop right now.
알겠어요 알겠어요 지금 숍이 굉장히 소란스럽네요
First of all, it's very flashy
일단 굉장히 화려한
I brought the most gorgeous palette I have.
내가 가지고 있는 가장 화려한 팔레트로 가져 왔어요
-Why did you bring the palette? - MAC
- 팔레트는 왜 가져 왔어요? - MAC
- Isn't eyeliner enough? - As expected from a MAC girl
- 아이라이너만 있으면 되는 거 아니에요? - 역시 MAC 걸
You should have eyeliner and eye color
아이라이너하고 눈동자 색깔 있어야 할 거 아니야
But I have a short forehead here, between my eyebrows and my eyes.
근데 제가 여기가 좀 짧은 편이에요, 눈썹과 눈 사이가
- I can do it really well - So it might be a little difficult.
- 내가 진짜 잘 할 수 있는데 - 그래서 좀 어려우실 거예요
I have no eyes
눈이 없어가지고요
Yes? What did you say?
네? 뭐라고요?
- But you really have to do it in moderation. - Okay, okay.
- 근데 진짜 적당히 해줘야 돼 - 알겠어요 알겠어요
Seriously, it's not a piece of paper
진짜 언니, 도화지가 아니에요
Oh my gosh
아 미치겠네
- But two people have to do it - But
- 근데 둘이 해야 되니까 - 근데
- I have to do it quickly / - That's right - That's right
- 빨리 해야겠다 / - 그니까 - 맞아맞아
- I want to cry - No, I'm crying
- 나 울고 싶어 - 아니 피어나
- But if you're going to do it, you have to do it right, right? - You have to do it right.
- 근데 할 거면 제대로 해야 될 거 아니야 그렇죠? - 제대로 해야 돼요
- That's true - Eunchae, it's the same.
- 그거는 맞는데 - 은채야 똑같이 되는 거야
- Even if you just close it, you'll become like me - Even if you close it, it'll be like Eunchae
- 그냥 감고 있어도 너처럼 되는 거야 - 감아도 은채
-Eun-chae even with her eyes closed-It's really not her business, everyone's in chaos right now
- 눈 감아도 은채 - 진짜 자기 일 아니라고 다 지금 난리가 났습니다
Seriously, I'm in the same situation
진짜 나도 똑같잖아 상황이
- What are you talking about, sis? - I told you I brought this.
- 뭔소리예요 언니 - 나 이거 가져왔다니까
Sister, you are pretty now
언니는 예쁘잖아 지금
- I brought this because I have to do this. - You just need to put a pack on this face.
- 나 이거 해야 되니까 가져왔어 - 언니는 이 얼굴에 팩만 하면 되잖아
Close your eyes, just close them.
눈 감으세요 그냥, 감으실게요
Yes, can you come a little closer?
네, 이거 조금 가까이 오실래요?
- You may feel a little shaky due to the magnesium deficiency issue. - You may feel a little shaky.
- 마그네슘 부족 이슈로 인해 조금 떨릴 수도 있어요 - 조금 떨릴 수 있어요
I might be a little nervous too. Okay, now open your eyes first.
저도 조금 떨릴 수 있어요 자 이제 눈을 먼저
Wait a minute, I won't laugh
잠시만, 웃지 않으실게요
I'll hold back my laughter
웃음 참으실게요
- I'm going - Mom, Mom
- 갑니다 - 엄마 엄마
- Mom - Mom
- 엄마
- A little bigger than your eyes - Don't rock the chair
- 너의 눈보다 조금 더 크게 - 의자 흔들지 마세요
why
왜
- I hope Eunchae doesn't see it until then - Close your eyes for a moment
- 은채가 안 봤으면 좋겠어 될 때까지 - 잠깐만 눈 감고 있으세요
- Okay - Yeah
- 그러게 - 응
- Keep it on, or don't look in the mirror. - That's right. / - Keep it on.
- 계속 감고 있어, 아니면 거울 보지 마 - 그러게 / - 감고 있어
- No, please make it pretty, unnie. - Just look down.
- 아니 언니 예쁘게 해줘 그래도 - 아래만 봐
A bit like a cat
약간 고양이처럼
- You're a total cat right now - But please do it with pretty eyes
- 완전 고양이 상인데 지금 - 예쁜 눈으로 해주세요 그래도
Yeah, you have such pretty eyes, they're so long and big.
응 너무 예쁜 눈이야, 완전 길쭉하고 큰 눈이야
Don't worry
걱정마셔
I'm good at drawing.
나 그림 잘 그리잖아
Shout Out to KBS KPOP
샤라웃 투 KBS KPOP
- Is it KPOP KBS? KBS KPOP - Okay
- KPOP KBS인가? KBS KPOP - 오케이
'Idol Human Theater'
'아이돌 인간극장'
First, I'll just draw the eye base.
일단 눈 베이스만 그려볼게요
Your eyes are a bit big
좀 눈 많이 큰데
- That's a bit big. - It's really big. Really big.
- 그러게 좀 많이 큰데 - 진짜 커 진짜 커
- But the line is pretty - But it looks like a cat, a cat
- 근데 라인은 예뻐 - 근데 이렇게 고양이 상이네 고양이 상
Okay, what will happen when I open my eyes?
괜찮아, 이게 눈 뜨면 어떻게 될까?
Doesn't it look like a perfect line?
완전 라인처럼 보이는 거 아니야?
But don't you have to draw the eyebrows like this?
근데 이거 이렇게 눈썹도 그려야 되는 거 아니야?
- So, let's just get the basics down first. - Be quiet.
- 그니까 일단 일단 기본만 먼저 잡고 - 조용히 해
- How do I draw the eyeballs? I have to draw the eyeballs too. - Please be quiet.
- 눈알을 어떻게, 눈알도 그려야 돼 - 제발 조용히 해 다
Do you guys have a group like this? Is it really true?
여러분 이런 그룹이 있어요? 혹시 진짜로
- It's cute. - Have you seen it?
- 귀엽대 - 본 적 있으세요?
Now you've seen it, because we're doing it.
이제 본 적이 있는 거야, 우리가 하고 있으니까
I think it will be a live that will go down in history.
역사에 남을 라이브가 될 것 같습니다
And this is what I do and dance
하고 이거 하고 춤추는 거지
How are you filming now?
어떻게 찍고 있어 지금?
You are really so pretty right now
진짜 완전 예뻐요 지금
But honestly, doesn't this symmetry match up so well?
근데 이거 솔직히 대칭 너무 잘 맞지 않아?
But the symmetry is really good
근데 진짜 대칭 너무 잘 맞아
- What should I do? - Seriously, if I do this much, I'll have makeup like this.
- 어떡해 - 진짜 여기까지하면 이런 메이크업 있어
Now all I have to do is draw the pupils
이제 눈동자만 그리면 돼
There really is makeup like this
이런 메이크업 있어 진짜로
- Wow, so pretty - It's like a pictorial right now
- 와 너무 예뻐 - 지금 완전 화보
First of all, first of all, then I will make the pupils for you.
일단 일단 먼저 그러면 내가 눈동자를 만들어 줄게
- Pupil - No cotton swabs here?
- 눈동자 - 면봉 없죠 여기?
- Cotton swab - I think I'm going to cry
- 면봉은 - 눈물 날 거 같아요
- Are you about to cry? Are you so touched? - I have wet tissues.
- 눈물 날 거 같아요? 너무 감격스러워서? - 물티슈는 있는데
now...
지금...
- No cotton swabs. - You can't open your eyes, right? Not yet. / - No, you can't.
- 면봉은 없네요 - 눈뜨면 안 되죠? 아직 / - 네 안돼요
Yes, yes, there are cotton swabs
있어요 있어요 면봉 있어요
When will it be?
언제 거죠?
It's a bit like this...
조금 이렇게 상태...
- It's been a while - Then it's okay.
- 조금 된 건데 - 그러면 괜찮아요
- It's new, but please use only this side. The other side... - It's new, it's new.
- 새 거예요 근데 이쪽만 쓰세요 반대쪽을... - 새 거, 새 건데
- Here - Yes, yes, use that.
- 여기 - 네네 그쪽 쓰세요
Are you crying?
눈물이 나나요?
- I'm so touched - Yes, I'll write it there.
- 너무 감동해서 - 네, 거기 써요
There are too many, okay guys
너무 많아서, 오케이 자 여러분
- Whether the eye color is pink, purple or glitter - The eye color is
- 눈동자 색을 핑크색, 보라색 아니면 반짝이 색으로 할지 - 눈동자는
- It's white / - This needs to be voted on / - This needs to be voted on / - Vote
- 흰색이죠 / - 투표 받아야 돼요 - 이거 투표 받아야 돼요 / - 투표
Or just something safe like brown?
아니면 좀 무난하게 그냥 브라운?
But this is a bit boring
근데 이건 좀 재미없긴 해
- I guess / - Pupils? - The pupils are brown.
- 아무래도 / - 눈동자? - 눈동자는 브라운
The pupils
눈동자를
What lenses do you want to wear today?
오늘 무슨 렌즈 끼고 싶어요?
What are your options?
선택권이 뭐예요?
- The choice is now - I wore brown lenses today.
- 선택권이 이제 - 오늘 브라운 렌즈를 꼈거든요 제가
"Is Chaewon doing Zhao too?"
"채원이 즈하도 하는 건가?"
- What are you talking about? - Look this way.
- 무슨 소리예요 - 이렇게 이쪽으로 봐
- Then you can't see it. - We're not punished.
- 그러면 안 보이잖아 - 저희는 벌칙 아니에요
- We did - Lens color
- 저희는 했잖아요 - 렌즈 색깔
- But do you want to do a little bit? - This? / - Or
- 근데 조금 하고 싶지? - 이거요? / - 아니면
- No, I don't want to. - This one? Or this one?
- 아니, 안 하고 싶어 - 이거요? 아니면 이거요?
Let's do this Let's do this
이걸로 하시죠 이걸로
- You want to do it, Zha? - I like it too.
- 너 해, 즈하 하고 싶어? - 역시 좋아요
- I'm curious - I'll do it next time.
- 난 궁금한데 - 다음 해줄게요
Zha is curious
즈하 궁금하대
Do you want to do it too?
즈하도 하고 싶어?
- Zha, do you want to do it? - Zha wants to do this too...
- 즈하 너 할래? - 즈하도 하고 싶어서 이런 거...
- That's why / - Zha is always like this - I want to receive it together
- 그니까 괜히 / - 즈하 항상 이렇다 - 같이 받고 싶어가지고
From the beginning, she kept saying, "My eyes are really good, so I do things like this."
아까부터 계속 옆에서 "내 눈이 진짜 좋다 이런 거 하기에"
- Appeal Appeal - You should have switched with me back then, sis
- 어필 어필 중 - 나랑 그때 바꿨어야 됐어 언니
I changed it
바꿔버렸네
Wow you guys are really sparkly
와 여러분 정말 반짝입니다
- MAC, I guess - MAC, I guess
- 아무래도 MAC
Fullme like this
풀메 이렇게
Oh, whose car is that
앗 차가 누구야
Don't keep putting your hand in
자꾸 손 넣지 마
The problem is that there is a hole.
구멍이 있는 게 문제죠
Draw the pupils
눈동자를 그립니다
Can you see it?
보이려나?
- Boldly - But you're drawing the border, right?
- 진하게 - 근데 그 테두리를 그려주시는 거죠?
I have to draw it
그려야지
- It looks like a lens, but really - Oh, it looks like a lens
- 렌즈 같아 근데 진짜 - 오 렌즈 같아
I'll close my eyes and relax.
눈 감으실게요, 힘 푸실게요
I should do it like this
이렇게 해야겠다
- It's real, it's scary - It's really scary
- 진짜 같아, 무서워 - 진짜 무서워
- I'm scared - Just a moment
- 무서워 - 진짜 잠시만
- It really looks like eyes, really. - Why? Does it look real?
- 진짜 눈 같아, 진짜 - 왜? 진짜 같아?
Just once, just once, just once
한번만 한번만 한번만
- Really keep looking at me - Stay still
- 진짜 계속 쳐다봐 - 가만 있어 봐
- It looks like real eyes / - It looks real - Is it scary?
- 진짜 눈 같아 / - 진짜 같아 - 무서운데?
- But the details are still - a little bit
- 근데 아직 디테일이 아직 - 조금
I'm a little scared
조금 무서워요
I'm really a bit scared
진짜 좀 많이 무서워요
- I have to see the comments - This is really awesome
- 난 댓글 봐야지 - 대박이다 진짜 이렇게
Please read the comments
댓글 좀 봐주세요
"lol"
"ㅋㅋㅋㅋ"
- "I'm scared" - "I'm scared"
- "무서워" - "무서워"래
- "Wow" - "Wow"
- "와우"
But really, it'll be over in 5 minutes
근데 진짜 5분이면 끝이에요
"Eunchae, don't cry when you see me"
"은채야 보고 울지 마"래
- No - "I'm scared"
- 아니야 - "무서워"
- Scary - Scary
- 무서워 - 무섭대
Pupil
동공
- Wait a minute - I'm scared
- 잠시만 - 무서워
- Just a moment - Then
- 그러면
- But this lens frame is like this - So, the frame needs to be framed.
- 근데 이 렌즈 테두리 이렇게 - 그니까 테두리 테두리 해야지
- Draw it, draw it - I need to draw a border
- 그려줘 그려줘 - 테두리를 해줘야 돼요
- Anyway, don't laugh, don't laugh - Not yet, it's not finished yet, sis
- 아무래도, 웃기지 마 웃기지 마 - 아직이야, 아직 미완성이야 언니
- Don't make me laugh. My hands are shaking. - Why are you here? Your face is shaking.
- 웃기지 마 나 이거 손 떨려 - 왜 여기 있어 얼굴이
You're not crying, are you?
우는 거 아니죠?
Yunjin Ah, you're doing well
윤진아, 잘 한다
Good job, you practiced, right?
잘 한다, 너 연습했지?
Sister, this was your dream, this was your dream
언니 꿈이었대 이게, 자기 꿈이었대
Since I was young
어렸을 때부터
- I need to put some dots here too - You're really good
- 여기도 좀 점을 좀 찍어야겠다 - 진짜 잘해
My sister said this was her dream since she was little
언니가 어렸을 때부터 이게 꿈이었대
Really good
진짜 잘해
Please draw a little dot
점도 조금 그려주세요
Could you please take a picture of this hand that is tightly holding my forehead?
내 이마를 꽉 잡은 이 손을 좀 찍어주실래요?
I guess
아무래도
- Wow, that's awesome, but you're good at it. - It's scary.
- 와 대박이다 근데 잘한다 - 무서워
Hey, good job
야 잘한다
- No, it looks more real when you look at it on the screen like this. - It looks real.
- 아니 이렇게 화면에 봐야 더 뭔가 진짜 같아 - 진짜 같아
- Look at the screen - It looks real
- 화면에서 봐야
You yourself are a bit like a painting
너 자체가 약간 그림 같아
scared
무서워
- It's time to be pretty, it's time to be pretty. - I'm scared, Eunchae.
- 이제 예뻐질 시간이에요, 예뻐질 시간이에요 - 무서워, 은채야
- I haven't put on any eye makeup yet. - Yeah, I haven't done it yet.
- 눈 화장 안 했어 아직 - 응 아직 안 했어
- Now I have eyes - Now I have eyes
- 이제 눈이 생긴 거야 - 이제 눈이 생긴 거고
Now I will draw the double eyelids and eyelashes.
이제 내가 그 쌍꺼풀이랑 속눈썹을 그려드릴게요
- Eunchae, please smile / - Today is Legend Live - It's Legend?
- 은채야, 제발 웃어줘 / - 오늘 레전드 라이브다 - 레전드인데?
But can I see this?
근데 내가 이걸 볼 수 있는 거야?
- Do you have to close your eyes to see it? - Yeah, I can't see it.
- 눈을 감아야 보이는 건가? - 그러게, 못 보겠네
- I'll take a picture for you - You'll never see yourself again
- 사진 찍어줄게 - 자신을 영원히 못 봐요
Eunchae, our eyes are meeting right now
은채야 우리 눈이 마주치고 있어 지금
- That's fun too - Here it is.
- 그것도 재밌는데 - 여기 있구나
I have to film myself doing that this is tick*
나 그거 했던 거 찍어야 돼 이거 틱*
You know what that is, not making eye contact?
그니까, 눈 마주치치 않기 그거 뭔지 아시죠?
You have to play this game while drinking water and not making eye contact
눈 마주치면 안 되는 게임 물 머금고 해야 돼
- Bring water. Water, water standby. - Really?
- 물 가져와 물, 물 스탠바이 - 진짜 가져와?
Should I bring it?
가져올까?
Good job
잘한다
It's so so good
너무 너무 좋다
Makeup
분장
scared
무서워
- No, it's really scary when you look at it from here. - But why are you so good at it?
- 아니 여기서 보면 진짜 무서워 - 근데 왜 이렇게 잘해?
I feel like my eyes are going to twitch
눈에 경련 올 것 같아요
- Once - I'm almost done.
- 한번 - 난 거의 완성이야
Do you want to open your eyes?
눈 뜰래?
- But why does this reach my eyebrows? - When I open my eyes, this
- 근데 왜 눈썹까지 이게 닿지? - 눈 뜨면 근데 이게
- I'm afraid it'll spread. - Oh, I'm afraid it'll spread.
- 번질까 봐 - 아 번질까 봐 그러네
I could feel the texture all the way to my eyebrows
눈썹까지 촉감이 닿았어요
It looks more realistic from a distance
멀리서 보니까 더 그럴싸해
- Wait a minute, wait a minute, not yet, not yet - Smile, smile
- 잠시만 잠시만 아직 아직이야 - 웃어 웃어
The pupil is still a little dilated
동공이 아직 조금
- Should it be darker? - Should it be darker?
- 더 진해야 돼? - 더 진해야 돼
I can't see it well on camera
잘 안 보인다 카메라에
Where is the camera?
어디 있어 카메라?
- Wow, I love it so much - It's awesome.
- 와 너무 맘에 들어 - 대박이다
Oh my god
오 마이 갓
This is really awesome
진짜 대박인데
I wish I could capture it beautifully
피어나가 예쁘게 캡처해줬으면 좋겠어요
- The pretty part. - Pretty.
- 예쁜 부분을요 - 예뻐
They're all pretty, what should I do?
다 예쁜데 어떡하죠?
No, Eunchae's face itself looks a bit like a painting right now
아니 은채 얼굴 자체가 약간 그림 같아 지금
Because the eyes are drawn like that
눈을 저렇게 그려 놓으니까
You really look like a doll.
너 진짜 인형 같다
The under eyelashes are awesome though
언더 속눈썹 대박이다 근데
- That's why - No one grows up this well.
- 그니까 - 이렇게 잘 자라는 사람 없어
Do you have more lower lashes?
언더 속눈썹이 더 많은데?
Under eyelashes are actually my eyebrows
언더 속눈썹이라는 게 실제로 내 눈썹
Real, real eyelashes
실제요 실제 속눈썹
- Is that what it looks like now? - Yeah.
- 그게 그렇게 보이는 거야 지금? - 응
You did so well
너무 잘했다
- No, really - Well done
- 아니 진짜 - 잘했다는 게
No really
아니 진짜로
- Really - Really
- 진짜로
A bit like that
약간 그런 쪽으로
It's like a real emoticon
진짜 이모티콘 같아
Laugh laugh laugh
웃어 웃어 웃어
Aren't you opening your eyes?
눈 뜨고 있는 거 아니야 이거?
But this is so good
근데 이거 너무 좋다
Crazy
미쳤다
- I shouldn't sleep, but when I'm too sleepy - Wait a minute, I'm just going to pack
- 졸면 안 되는데, 너무 잠이 올 때 - 잠시만, 난 그냥 팩
Just pack
팩을 그냥
It's so good okay
너무 좋다 오케이
Is it done?
된 거예요?
Can I open my eyes slightly and comb my bangs?
눈 살짝만 떠서 앞머리 좀 빗어도 돼요?
But it's so good
근데 너무 괜찮은데
But aren't the spaces between your eyebrows too wide?
근데 미간이 너무 넓은 거 아니야?
Eunchae, but it's a little bit gathered inside the eyeball.
은채야, 근데 약간 눈알 안쪽에 모였잖아
Are your eyes closed?
눈이 모여있어?
- Really? - No, no
- 그래? - 아니야 아니야
I feel like I'm looking inside something
뭔가 안쪽 보고 있는 거 같아
Are you okay? Does my face look okay right now?
괜찮아요? 제 얼굴 지금 모습이 괜찮아요?
It's totally okay, Eunchae
완전 괜찮아요 은채
I really think it's just popping up
진짜 그냥 뜨고 있는 거 같아
I think it's really hot
진짜 뜨고 있는 거 같아
- I think my eyes are open - You did really well, I think I'm crazy
- 눈 뜨고 있는 거 같아 - 진짜 너무 잘했다 미쳤나 봐
Something new like this
이런 걸로 새로운 약간
I feel like my eyes are really open
진짜 눈 뜨고 있는 거 같아
How did you take pictures of the jacket like this?
어떻게 이렇게 재킷 찍어?
- But really - possible possible
- 근데 진짜 - 가능 가능
Why did you do this so well?
이거 왜 이렇게 잘했어?
Did you practice?
연습했지?
- I've been doing a lot of image training at home now. - Peace, peace.
- 집에서 이제 이미지 트레이닝 많이 했죠 - 피스 해줘 피스
Peace Peace
피스 피스
You're cute, our Eunchae
귀여워요 우리 은채 씨
What kind of lens is it?
렌즈 뭐예요?
- But how do you wink? - What kind of lenses are those?
- 근데 윙크는 어떻게 해요? - 렌즈 뭐예요?
Just take a picture
일단 사진 찍어 봐
Okay okay look show it to Eunchae
오케이 오케이 봐봐 은채한테 보여줘
- Eunchae-ya - Yes? Are you opening your eyes?
- 은채야 - 네? 눈 떠요?
When you open your eyes, you can't see it?
눈 뜨면 근데 안 보이지 않아?
It's so real
진짜 같아
Close your eyes for a moment.
잠시만 눈 감아 봐
Come on
떠 봐
- Wow but really - Wow that's amazing
- 와 근데 진짜 - 와 신기하다
It's so real
진짜 같아
oh my god
어떡해
Okay, I think Eunchae is perfect to this extent.
자, 은채 이 정도면 저는 완벽하다고 봅니다
- Wow, wait a minute, wait a minute, this is amazing - It's amazing, even when I open my eyes
- 와 잠시만 잠시만 대박이다 - 신기하다 눈 떠도
- I think it's really, really good. - Where did you go? My...
- 너무 너무 괜찮은 거 같아요 - 어디 갔지? 내...
- Where is Oppa? - Oppa is here, here
- 오빤쮸 어디 - 오빤쮸 여기 여기
Here here here
여기 여기 여기
- Now let's change seats. Next - Next
- 이제 자리를 바꾸실게요 다음 - 다음
- Should I wait like this? - I
- 이러고 대기해요 저? - 저는
- Then - wait
- 그러면 - 대기하고
You can close your eyes
눈 감으셔도 돼요
Would you please close your eyes and wait here next to me?
눈 감고 여기 옆에서 대기하실래요?
Sit down
앉아서
Or should I take a picture of that? That
아니면 그걸 찍을까? 그거
- I need to take a selfie - while waiting
- 셀카 찍어야지 - 대기하는 동안
I'll finish it really quickly
저는 뭐 진짜 금방 끝나요
- Yes, just paste it. - That's right.
- 네 그냥 붙이기만 하면 - 맞습니다
Really pack
진짜 팩하는
Where is this?
이거 어디 거예요?
- It's Primera - Primera
- 프리메라입니다 - 프리메라
Primera
프리메라
Looks like very good quality
굉장히 퀄리티가 좋아보여요
- Really big - I like this
- 진짜 커 - 이거 좋아요
- Oppachoo - Oppachoo
- 오빤쮸
Oppaju
오빤쥬
Next is Sakura
다음은 사쿠라
Wait a minute, do I have to show you this?
잠시만 근데 이 모습을 보여줘야 되나
Should I take a look first?
내가 먼저 봐줄까?
- Isn't it? - Appearance check?
- 아닌가? - 외모 체크?
- Check your appearance - I'll be checking your appearance.
- 외모 체크 - 외모 체크 하고 있을게요
Appearance check
외모 체크
Your face looks like a seal
얼굴이 물개 같은데 되게
fur seal
물개
seal
[일] 물개
- It's pretty. - It's pretty.
- 예쁘네 - 예뻐요
It's pretty
예쁘네
What kind of punishment is this?
이게 무슨 벌칙이야
It's a shame I should have done it on my way to work
출근길에 했어야 되는데 아쉽다
- We've been recording too much - too much, that's a bit...
- 우리가 사녹을 너무 - 너무 그거는 좀...
- Keep doing Sanok in the morning - Yeah, yeah
- 사녹을 계속 아침에 해가지고 - 맞아 맞아
- The timing was a bit vague, yes - and there was an event going on.
- 시간이 좀 애매하긴했어, 맞아 - 그리고 행사도 있어가지고
No, wait a minute
안 돼, 잠시만
This
이거를
- Real vitamins, full of vitamins - That's right, that's right / - Take it out?
- 진짜 비타민, 비타민 가득 - 맞아 맞아 / - 빼드려?
Because this is separate
이게 분리 돼 있어서
Wow this smells so good
와 이거 향이 너무 좋아요
- Pretty, pretty - Looks good
- 예뻐 예뻐 - 좋아 보인다
Looks really good
진짜 좋아 보인다
- It's like a mask. - Really? / - Yeah.
- 마스크 같아 - 그래요? / - 응
Take them one by one
하나씩 가져가
How many are inside?
안에 몇 개 있어?
- There are many, there are many - It's fast.
- 많아 많아 - 빠르네
- Okay - The end
- 됐어 - 끝
it's okay?
됐어?
- My sister and I should do that. - It's still pretty.
- 언니랑 나랑 그거 하자 - 그래도 예쁘네
Yeah, two, two
그래 둘이 둘이
Let's take a picture now. Let's take a picture now. Should I bring water?
지금 찍자 지금 찍자 물 가져올까?
It's fun when there's water, water, water
물 물 물이 있어야 재밌는데
- Can you actually squirt water? - Actually
- 실제로 뿜을 수도 있어요? 물을? - 실제로
Should I bring you some water?
물 가져올까?
- Is this it? - Two would be enough?
- 이건가? - 두 개 있으면 되겠지?
- Yes - Yeah
- 네 - 응
There was no sound or anything?
사운드 같은 거 없었지?
- I don't know - I think it was just taken
- 모르겠어 - 그냥 그냥 찍은 거 같아
- Just take a picture / - Later - Okay, okay
- 그냥 찍고 / - 나중에 - 오케이 오케이
I really like this, this
이거 진짜 좋아요, 이게
- suddenly - promotion / - promotion
- 갑자기 - 홍보 / - 홍보
Contains vitatinol
비타티놀이 들어가 있습니다
Are you okay, Eunchae?
은채 씨는 잘 보이세요?
Need to lower it a bit more
좀 더 낮춰야 돼
- Two of you have capture time - Two of you capture, okay
- 둘이 캡처 타임 가져 - 둘이 캡처, 그래
Time for just the two of us
둘 만의 시간
You're a makeup artist, come here.
메이크업 아티스트잖아요, 여기 와주세요
Thank you thank you thank you
감사합니다 감사합니다 감사합니다
thank you
감사합니다
Please take lots of pretty pictures
많이 예쁘게 찍어주세요
My work
저의 작품
- Thank you. - Is the water coming?
- 감사합니다 - 물 오고 있죠?
- Coming - Like this
- 오고 있습니다 - 이걸 이렇게
- Settings? - I need to see the reaction.
- 세팅? - 반응을 좀 봐야겠다
But how do you do it? Do it like this
근데 어떻게 하는 거야? 이렇게 하고 있다가
I have to open my eyes like this every once in a while
이렇게 한 번씩 눈을 떠야 되는데
- You can't open your eyes at the same time - But / - You can't make eye contact, so...
- 눈을 동시에 뜨면 안 돼 - 근데 / - 눈을 마주치면 안 돼, 그래서...
Let's practice
연습해보자
- Eyes - one, two, three
- 눈을 - 하나 둘 셋
- This won't do. - Then it won't do.
- 이러면 안 되는 거야 - 그럼 안 되는 거야
- This is not right. - But what is this?
- 근데 이게 뭐야
Sister Kura, I can't laugh
꾸라 언니 못 웃어요
If you laugh, it will fall off
웃으면 떼져요
Don't laugh, if you laugh...
웃으면 안 돼, 웃으면...
You look so funny when you laugh
너무 웃기게 생겼어 웃으면
All I can see is teeth
이빨밖에 안 보여
When you smile, only your teeth are visible
이빨밖에 안 보여 웃으면
- This is how you do it - That'll do it / - Okay, okay
- 이렇게 하는 거예요 - 그렇게 하면 됩니다 / - 오케이 오케이
It's so funny
너무 웃기네
We're really having fun...
우리 진짜 재밌게...
But when I open my eyes, there really isn't anything
근데 눈 뜨면 진짜 하나도
- Then I'll just do this - Then
- 그럼 나 그냥 이렇게 - 그럼
I can never hold it for a long time
절대 장시간으로 감을 수 없어
He said she digested everything by laughing
웃어서 소화가 다 됐대
- That's fortunate. - That's fortunate.
- 다행이네 - 다행입니다
- Thank goodness - "Yujam Group"
- "유잼 그룹"
Please spread the word that this is a fun group, everyone.
유잼 그룹인 거 널리널리 소문 좀 퍼뜨려주세요 여러분
- You're here / - Okay - You're here Water
- 오셨다 / - 오케이 - 오셨다 물
You have arrived
오셨다
Now the water...
이제 물을...
thank you
감사합니다
Wait a minute, are you doing this right?
잠시만, 제대로 해요?
- What if I really spit it out? - What if I really spit it out?
- 진짜 뿜으면 어떡해?
- We should just go like that. - Just go like that.
- 그대로 가야죠 뭐 - 그대로 뭐
I guess we should just go with that
그대로 가야죠 뭐
Yeah what
네 뭐
Don't you have that? The one you use when dyeing your hair?
없나? 그 염색할 때 쓰는 거?
- I think so? - I think so?
- 있을 거 같은데?
- Are you nervous? / - Yes. - Yes.
- 떨려? / - 있어 - 그래
I'll borrow it
빌릴게요
Are there only big ones?
큰 거밖에 없어?
I think I'll be here for a while
잠시만 여기 있을 거 같은데
- Are you doing it now? - Do it.
- 하는 거야 이제? - 하세요
Wait a minute, but what the heck
잠시만 근데 이러고, 무슨
It's like a ghost
유령 같아
what...
무슨...
I'm going crazy
미치겠다
There was one more, one more
하나 더 있었어, 하나 더
There is one
하나 있어
It's a bit small though
좀 작아 근데
What is this situation?
무슨 상황이죠 이게?
Where did the water go?
물 어디 갔지?
Why is this so funny
왜 이렇게 웃겨
- What? - But shouldn't two people sit together? / - That's right.
- 뭐가 - 근데 둘이 앉아야 되는 거 아니야? / - 그니까
- Sit here / - Sit here - Are you coming out?
- 앉아 여기에 / - 앉아 - 나오려나?
- No, let's do this - Let's do the small one.
- 아니 이거, 이걸로 하자 - 작은 걸로
- Sit down - One by one
- 앉으세요 - 하나씩
Isn't it too close? Just a moment.
너무 가까운 거 아니야? 잠시만
Please drink water
물을 마셔주세요
- Please hold it. - Please be the moderator in the middle.
- 머금어주세요 - 중간에서 사회자 해주세요
Just record this on video
그냥 이거 영상으로 찍고
- I'll have to edit it later - Okay, okay
- 나중에 편집해야겠다 - 좋아 좋아
okay
오케이
- Please drink some water. - Chaewon, please host. / - This is already funny. What should I do?
- 물을 머금어주세요 - 채원 씨가 사회 봐주세요 / - 벌써 웃긴데 어떡해?
- Chaewon, please proceed. - Why, why, why? / - A lot? A lot?
- 채원 씨가 진행해주세요 - 왜, 왜, 왜? / - 많이요? 많이요?
- Just something moderate? - Yes, something moderate enough to hold.
- 그냥 뭐 적당히? - 네 적당히 머금을 수 있을 만큼
- I'll leave this to Chaewon now. - Are you done?
- 이거는 이제 다 채원 씨에게 맡기겠습니다 - 되셨나요?
- Hold on - Now close your eyes.
- 참으세요 - 이제 눈을 감아주세요
Please close your eyes
눈을 감아주세요
To me?
나한테?
okay
알았어
- Close your eyes. - Okay, okay, okay.
- 눈을 감아주세요 - 좋아 좋아 좋아
- No, already - Really?
- 아니 벌써 - 진짜?
- I don't think Eunchae will work? - Eunchae, Eunchae
- 은채 안 될 거 같은데? - 은채야, 은채야
- Eunchae-ya - Let's start, one, two, three.
- 은채야 - 시작하겠습니다, 하나 둘 셋
I don't think Eunchae will work
은채 안 될 거 같은데
Eunchae
은채 씨
You have to play the game
게임 진행하셔야 됩니다
- But you have to show these eyes here - Kura unnie is totally...
- 근데 이 눈이 보여야 돼 여기서 - 꾸라 언니가 완전...
Okay okay okay
오케이 오케이 오케이
Swallow, swallow, swallow the water
삼키세요 삼키세요, 물 삼키세요
- I feel like I'm going to die. - You two need to stick together so I can see your eyes.
- 진짜 죽을 거 같아 - 좀 둘이 붙어서 이 눈이 보여야 돼
Making eye contact
눈 마주치는 게
A little further forward?
좀 더 앞으로?
Stick forward and stick to each other
앞으로 붙고 서로 서로 붙어
- This is so funny, what should I do? I really - This is fun when we stick together.
- 너무 웃긴데 어떡해? 나 진짜로 - 서로 붙어야 재밌어 이거
So funny
너무 웃겨
- I'm really laughing so hard, what should I do? - What should I do?
- 나 진짜 너무 웃긴데 어떡해 - 어떡해?
- Let's stick to each other like this. - Stick, stick together.
- 좀 서로 이렇게 붙을게요 - 붙어, 붙어야 돼
- Stick closer, stick closer - Can I do it once without water?
- 더 붙어, 더 - 일단 물 없이 한 번만 해도 돼요?
- Okay, okay, I got it - Practice without water.
- 오케이 오케이, 알겠어 - 물 없이 연습
- Wait, don't laugh. - No, I'm shaking like this because I'm laughing.
- 잠시만, 웃으면 안 돼 - 아니 웃어서 이렇게 떨려
I will do it
할게
start
시작
Let's decide who to start with
누구부터 시작한다는 정하자
Okay let's start with Eunchae
오케이 은채부터 시작해
- I'm doing it - Okay
- 한다 진짜 - 오케이
- Really? - Really?
- 진짜로? - 진짜해
Seriously, what should I do?
나 진짜 어떡해
- Eunchae, you can do this. - Do this...
- 은채야 할 수 있어 넌 - 이거를 좀...
near?
가까이?
- What should I do? - Like this
- 나 진짜 어떡하지? - 이렇게까지
A video that will go down in history
역사에 남을 영상
- No, why don't you just drink water? - Eunchae-ya / - Why not already?
- 아니 왜 물만 마시면 - 은채야 / - 왜 벌써 안 돼?
I got a disease where I just drink water and laugh
물만 마시면 웃는 병이 생겼어요
I think I really need to give Eunchae a cup
은채한테는 진짜 컵을 줘야 될 거 같아
From Eunchae, from Eunchae
은채부터, 은채부터
start
시작
Hey, Eunchae, I don't know if your eyes are open or not.
야 근데 은채야 넌 눈을 뜬 건지 안 뜬 건지 모르겠어
- There's chaos - I don't know if you've seen it or not
- 난리가 나버렸어 - 본지 안 본지 모르겠어
- Hey Eunchae - Eunchae
- 야 은채야 - 은채야
- The match is not possible, the match is not possible - The game is not progressing right now.
- 대결이 안 돼요, 대결이 안 돼요 - 지금 게임 진행이 안 됩니다
teacher
선생님
really
진짜
Are you okay?
괜찮은 거지?
This is so funny, what should I do? Seriously
너무 웃겨 어떡해 진짜로
- Are you really open your eyes or not? - Just look at me once, Yunjin.
- 정말 눈을 떴는지 안 떴는지 - 한 번만 봐봐 윤진이
- Mine? / - Did you take a picture? - Just to see if the amount came out or not
- 내 거? / - 찍었어? - 이걸로 분량이 나왔는지 안 나왔는지만
- Is the amount out? - Discuss the amount / - The amount
- 분량이 나왔는지 - 분량 토론해 / - 분량이
But no one could spit it out
근데 그 아무도 뿜지 못 해서
So, without spitting anything out
그러니까, 뭐 뿜지도 않고
- Just one more time - No, just one more time
- 그냥 진짜 딱 한 번만 - 아니 진짜 한 번만 더
- Don't laugh - Seriously
- 웃지 마 - 진짜
- One more time - It's okay to spit it out
- 한 번 더 - 뿜어도 괜찮아요
calm down
진정해
- Can you calm down with this? - Yes, I'll leave work like this.
- 진정할 수 있겠냐고 이걸로 - 네, 이러고 퇴근이요
Come closer
가까이 오실게요
I feel like it's going to go into my nose
코에 들어갈 거 같아
start
시작
Are you still doing it?
아직도 하고 있어요?
what are you doing
뭐 하는 거야
If this continues, I'll hear a noise
이러다 사레 들리겠어요
- But it really holds water well. - Yes, up to here.
- 근데 물을 진짜 잘 머금고 있는다 - 네 여기까지
I think I would have just spit it out
나는 바로 뿜었을 거 같아
Want to try?
해볼래?
Want to try it? Together?
해볼래? 같이?
Yoonjin and Eunchae, try it
윤진이랑 은채가 해봐
- I have so much mental strength - Do it, do it, do it quickly / - My sister
- 나는 너무 정신력이 강해가지고 - 해봐 해봐, 빨리 해봐 / - 언니는
- Sister, so you hold back your laughter well - It doesn't mean anything, hold back well, hold back well
- 언니는, 그러니까 웃는 거 잘 참아 - 별 의미가 없어, 잘 참아 잘 참아
- That's right / - Come here - I'm so used to it now.
- 그러게 / - [영] 이리 와 - 이제 너무 익숙했어
- Me? - Makeup artist
- 나? - 메이크업 아티스트
Makeup artist
메이크업 아티스트
On top of makeup...
화장 위에...
Look at your skin, your skin is suddenly
피부 봐, 피부가 갑자기
As a bonus
번외로
I'm scared, though?
저 두렵습니다만?
What if I squirt in your real face?
진짜 언니 얼굴에 뿜으면 어떡하지?
I'm really sorry
진짜 미안
Squirt squirt
뿜어 뿜어
- Hey, you put too much in. - You put too much in.
- 야 너무 많이 - 많이 넣었네
Are you taking a picture?
찍고 있지?
Eunchae... Eunchae...
은채가... 은채가...
Hey, squirt, squirt, squirt
야 뿜어, 뿜어 뿜어
It's fun if you spit it out
뿜어야 재밌지
Poem... Close your eyes
시... 눈을 감아요
- What is what? Eunchae first - Eunchae first, Eunchae first
- 뭐가 뭐가? 은채 먼저 - 은채부터, 은채부터
start
시작
Did you spit it out?
뱉었어요?
You didn't spit it out?
안 뱉었어?
One more time, one mall time
한 번 더, 원 몰 타임
Reset, reset
리셋, 리셋
start
시작
I'll stop here
여기까지 하겠습니다
End End
종료 종료
End, reset live end
종료, 리셋 라이브 종료
hi
안녕
- Just a moment - Why?
- [영] 잠시만 - 왜?
The live isn't over yet
라이브 아직 종료 아니야
- That's right, I didn't say 'CRAZY'. - Really?
- 맞아요 'CRAZY' 안 했어 - 그래?
- 'CRAZY', that's right, that's right - It has to be 'CRAZY'
- 'CRAZY', 맞네 맞네 - 'CRAZY' 해야 돼
- Video, video end - Video end
- 영상, 영상 종료 - 영상 종료
- It was good - My sister had her eyes closed, but her face was
- 좋았습니다 - 언니가 눈을 감고 있는데 얼굴이
It was good
좋았습니다
- Clean up - Wipe off some water
- 정리하고 - 물 좀 닦고
Let me wipe the water off.
물을 좀 닦겠습니다
- Seriously - so funny
- 진짜 - 너무 웃겨
There isn't much water though
물이 얼마 안 되네요 근데
- I couldn't spit out much water. - I was scared so I drank only a little.
- 네 물을 많이 뿜지 못했어요 - 쫄아서 조금만 먹었어요
I think so
그럴 거 같아
okay
오케이
It's hot all of a sudden
더워 갑자기
finally
마지막으로
The Last Serenade for Fearnot
피어나를 위한 마지막 세레나데
- Should I do this too? - This is the last one.
- 나도 해야 되나 이거? - 마지막입니다
- Should I do it while packing? - I have to, I have to.
- 팩 하면서 할까? - 해야 돼, 해야 돼
- Okay, I'm fine. - Are you okay?
- 오케이, 괜찮아 - 괜찮아?
You can do it in 5 seconds
5초 만에 할 수 있어요
okay
오케이
Verse 1
1절
Please take care of me, I'm dancing with my eyes closed
저를 배려해주세요, 저 눈 감고 추니까
- Are you really doing this with your eyes closed? - You really have to do this with your eyes closed.
- 진짜 눈 감고 하는 거예요? - 진짜 눈 감고 해야 돼요
The three of us
우리 세 명이
Let's move this chair a little bit
이거 의자를 조금 옮겨 놓고
great
좋습니다
It's completely brown
완전 갈색이 나
It suits you well
잘 어울려
- What color am I? - Okay.
- 나는 무슨 색이지? - 그니까
- What color is it, gray? - Gray / - It's gray.
- 뭔가 무슨 색인지, 회색? - 회색 / - 회색인데
- It's like gray - It's like blue-black
- 회색 같아 - 블루블랙이면서도
It looks like something brown, but I'm not sure
뭔가 갈색인 거 같으면서도, 잘 모르겠어요
The youngest is showing off his talents
막내 재롱잔치네
Is your beard graying?
수염이 허옇게 났어요?
okay
오케이
- Okay / - Okay - Okay?
- 됐어 / - 오케이 - 됐어요?
Please prepare
준비해주세요
The three of us are so normal
우리 셋 너무 정상이야
- Are you doing this with your eyes closed? - No, no.
- 다 눈 감고 하는 거야? - 아니 아니
I'm doing well
잘 하고 있어
Everyone is doing well
다들 잘한다
I know?
그러게?
Good job
잘한다
Why are you so good at this?
왜 이렇게 잘해?
You are so good
너무 잘한다
Our practice volume
우리의 연습량을
Where are you
어딨어
Isn't Eunchae so good?
은채 너무 잘하는 거 아니야?
Are you doing well? Are you doing well?
잘하지? 잘하지?
- You're so good - That's awesome.
- 너무 잘하잖아 - 대박이다
You're not really laughing, are you?
너 진짜 웃는 거 아니지?
- Are you holding it in? - Really?
- 감고 있는 거지? - 진짜
Move over, move over, move over
비켜 비켜, 비켜
Let's do the Eunchae part too
은채 파트까지 하자
Okay okay okay
좋아 좋아 좋아
Get out of the way, get out of the way
비켜 비켜
It's a jackpot
대박이야
- That's awesome - You did a great job
- 대박이다 - 너무 잘했다
how is it?
어때요?
- Your body is reacting. - Are you doing well?
- 몸이 반응하고 있다는 - 잘하네?
It was absolutely perfect
아주 완벽했습니다
- Thank you - Like this
- 감사합니다 - 이렇게 해서
- The penalty is over now finally - up to now / - finally
- 벌칙 끝났습니다 이제 드디어 - [일] 지금까지 / - 드디어
- So far - So far, it was Seraphim
- [일] 지금까지 - [일] 지금까지 르세라핌이었습니다
- I finally finished it - with this challenge.
- 드디어 다 했습니다 - 이번 챌린지로
- All finished - All clear
- 모두 다 끝냈습니다 - 모두 클리어입니다
- 'Idol Human Theater' - This is the end of 'CRAZY' activities
- '아이돌 인간극장' - 이걸로 'CRAZY' 활동이 끝났다고
- So, that was the 'CRAZY' promotion - The last episode is over / - Finally
- 그러니까, 지금까지 'CRAZY' 활동이었습니다 - 막방이 끝났습니다 / - 드디어
- Have you seen it? - It's over.
- 보셨나요 - 끝났습니다
- Thank you - Thank you
- 감사합니다
- Bye bye - Bye bye
- 빠이빠이
- Thank you Fearnot - Bye
- 고마워요 피어나 - 안녕
Eunchae, you turn it off, close your eyes
은채야 네가 꺼봐, 그 눈 감고
Please stay still
제발 가만히 있어봐
- No / - End - No no
- 아니야 / - 끝 - 아니 아니